http://www.wgte.org/privacy-policy

01:58:01
FM 91's online audio is listener supported.
Help support the stream. Donate now
You are hereHome / Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The Public Broadcasting Foundation of Northwest Ohio (WGTE Public Media) operates this website. You may contact us with questions or comments about the website by any of the following means:
Mail:Public RelationsWGTE Public Media PO Box 30 Toledo, OH 43614Telephone: (419) 380-4600
E-mail:  WGTE’s online privacy policy is guided by these basic principles:
We will not collect personally identifiable information from you, other than what you supply to us on a voluntary basis.
In order to participate in some activities, you might be asked to provide some personally identifiable information. This could be in connection with the following:
contest registration
subscription registration for services which require subscription (such as e-mail playlists)
applications for membership or membership information
volunteer registration
online transactions
content submissions including blogs, video and audio, item ratings, item tagging, etc.
WGTE Public Media will not disclose your personal information to any third party without first receiving your permission.
WGTE Public Media may use your personally identifiable information for activities explained above, for internal and marketing promotional purposes. We will always explain the extent of its use at the time you are asked to provide personal information. If you do not want this information to be collected or used by us for these purposes, you can simply "opt out." Under certain circumstances, opting out may prevent your participation in activities for which personal information is needed, as in contests.
About WGTEBoard of DirectorsClosed Captioned CertificationContact UsEmploymentFinancial InformationGovernanceMeeting MinutesMission and VisionPolicies and ProceduresPress RoomPrivacy PolicyProtect My Public MediaTerms of UseVolunteer at WGTEHoliday Specials
SCHEDULES
Television
Programs A-Z
TV Schedule
Production Services
Special Projects
Great Lakes Now
Nature's Path
